Alina Sargsyan

22 y.o, Minsk +37529 6559133 sargsyanalina98@gmail.com



Linguist. English teacher

Education:

Faculty: English Language Faculty

University: Minsk State Linguistic University

Modern Foreign Languages

About me:

Responsive, polite, I can easily find contact with people. I maintain business and professional contacts and have a creative mind. I have an active lifestyle. I read fiction, am interested in psychology and visit the pool. I am ready to work hard and in return get unique experience, professional development and personal growth.

Experience:

1. English teacher at school №. 9 in Minsk (practice)

- teach English, selecting teaching methods for each class

- made a plan-summary for lessons February - May

- prepared presentations 2020

- through practice, I improved my professional skills

English tutor

- individually worked with a child (9 years old)

- made up the material and plan for the class September 2019 – May 2020

- helped with homework

- engaged in in-depth language learning

Controller-cashier at the Pull&Bear store (Dana Mall)

- communicated with customers and stimulated sales

- participated in inventory and acceptance of goods September 2019

- August 2020 - engaged in servicing at the checkout and maintaining cash documents

- ensured the safety of the goods in the trading floor

4. Educator in the health camp «Dream»

- planned and organized educational activities in the unit

July 2018 – August 2018 - compiled and selected various methodological developments

- studied the peculiarities of each child's personality development

- created a favorable atmosphere in the squad

5. Wedding coordinator:

Passed an intensive training course "Wedding coordinator" from the company

- I was preparing for the event, making a plan for the wedding day

2018 - 2019

- worked with contractors

- worked on the wedding day